netlog.com 2013-06-12

# Privacy Statement

  * Code of Conduct
  * Privacy
  * Terms & conditions
  * Credits

Massive Media NV processes your personal data in conformity with this privacy policy and with the strict rules of Belgian and European data protection legislation.

This privacy policy is a part of our Terms & Conditions and should be read carefully, as it specifies which rights you have and how you can exercise your rights. Any use of the Netlog website, hereinafter referred to as 'Netlog' or the 'Website', implies the entire acceptance of this privacy policy. 

## Types of personal data we collect

  * **Public information uploaded by you:**
    * information in your profile, blogs, shouts, pictures, videos, events, music, links 
    * messages sent to other users, as well as ratings, shouts and contributions to another user's guestbook
    * links to your friends and groups
  * **Private information uploaded by you:**
    * settings and administrative data such as your username and password, skin, logs, credits and shortcuts
    * your privacy settings, whitelist and blacklist
  * **History and logs**
    * time, date and URL of all Netlog pages visited by you
    * the URL of the referring websites
    * the searches you perform on Netlog
    * technical information regarding your internet browser and computer 

## Purposes for which we use your personal data

We use your personal data to:

  * publish the information intended to be made public by you, under the conditions specified in your privacy settings
  * allow you to correctly use the Website in accordance with your settings
  * perform general customer administration 
  * send you communications about the Website, as well as our other products and services 
  * provide you with advertisements tailored to your profile 
  * investigate fraud and infringements of our Code of Conduct
  * generate anonymous statistics about the (users of the) Website, to improve the Website or convey statistical information to third parties

## Storage term and location

Massive Media NV applies the following storage terms:

  * **Information uploaded by you:** stored during a period of 6 months after you delete this information, or delete your account. (Note: you can delete your account at any time. If you do not log in on your account during a period of two years, your account will be deleted automatically.)
  * **History and logs:** stored during a period of 6 months after the history item or log event was created
  * **Cookies:** cookies used on the Website have a maximum lifetime of 100 days. 

Your personal data may be stored in a country outside the EU.

## How your personal data are shared with third parties

  * Third parties can access all information intended to be made public by you, under the conditions specified in your privacy settings.
  * We hate spam as much as you do. Your e-mail address is never shared by us with any third party. 
  * For the purpose of targeted advertisements, we share your browser type, IP address, current and previous URL you are visiting (and search query), age, gender, and geographical location with our advertisement provider. This information may subsequently be used by other websites for the display and management of targeted advertisements. 
  * We never share any of your other personal data with any third party, unless you give your explicit permission. 
  * We may, however, provide access to your personal data in case of illegal use, or when we receive orders from legal authorities.

## Cookies and web-bugs

  * The Website uses cookies to identify you as a user of the Website, to remember your preferred language and to facilitate navigation on the Website. 
  * You can disable cookies in your internet browser, although some parts of the Website will then no longer function correctly. 
  * The Website also uses a cookie and an AdPath pixel ("web-bug") to allow third parties to tailor advertisements to your profile. 

## Your rights

  * You can get access to your personal data free of charge (and correct it, or have it corrected, where relevant). 
  * You can object to the use of your personal data for direct marketing purposes. 

## Contact information

**Massive Media NV**  
E. Braunplein 18  
B-9000 Gent  
Belgium

Fax +32 2 400 43 20

VAT BE 0859635972  
VAT Nr. BE 859635972

privacy-en@netlog.com

Last changed on February 26, 2009.

* * *
